Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Hockey photos
    - 1998-1999
      - Western Michigan 1/16/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Ohio State 2/06/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Miami 2/26-27/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Bowling Green 3/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Ohio State 3/19/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Northern Michigan 3/20/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
    - 1999-2000
      - U-Mass-Lowell 10/15-16/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Yale 10/30/1999, negatives, contact sheets, prints (Box 37)
      - Ohio State 11/05/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Lake Superior State 11/19-20/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Minnesota 11/26/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Bowling Green 12/04/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Ohio State 1/29/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Ferris State 2/05/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Western Michigan 2/12/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Michigan State 2/26/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Bowling Green 3/04/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Nebraska 3/17/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
    - 2000-2001
      - Colgate 10/06/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - North Dakota 10/07/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 37)
      - Alaska Fairbanks 11/18/2000, negatives (Box 37)
      - Unidentified, negatives (Box 37)
  - U-M Wrestling photos
    - 1972-1973
      - Michigan State 2/1973, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1973-74
      - Ohio State 1/05/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1974-75
      - Penn State 12/1974, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Iowa 2/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Michigan State 2/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1975-76
      - Ohio 12/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Michigan State 12/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - ITWA Tournament 12/21/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Illinois & Ohio State 1/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Purdue 1/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1976-1977
      - Penn State 12/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Southern Illinois 1/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Iowa State 1/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Minnesota 2/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1977-1978
      - Indiana 1/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Michigan State 2/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Wisconsin 2/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Ohio State 2/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Big Ten Championships 3/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Lehigh 1/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Iowa 2/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Minnesota 2/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Michigan State 2/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1979-1980
      - Michigan State 11/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Kent State 12/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Indiana 1/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Purdue 1/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Hofstra 1/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Indiana State 1/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Ohio State 2/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1980-1981
      - Clarion State 12/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Lehigh 1/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Northern Illinois 1/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Northwestern 1/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Iowa State 2/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Ball State 2/1981, slides (Box 38)
    - 1981-82
      - Michigan State 11/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Penn State 12/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Cleveland State 1/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Indiana 1/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Big Ten tournament 2/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
      - Ohio State 2/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 38)
    - 1982-1983
      - Wolverine Open 11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Northwestern 1/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Iowa 2/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Minnesota 2/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Iowa State 2/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1983-84
      - Penn State 12/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Arizona State & Indiana 1/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Michigan State 1/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Purdue 1/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Ohio State 2/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1984-85
      - Wolverine Open 11/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Central Michigan 12/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Northwestern 1/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Morgan State 1/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Lehigh 1/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Penn State 2/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Iowa State 2/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Minnesota 2/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Northern Iowa 2/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1985-1986
      - Indiana 1/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Notre Dame 1/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Michigan State 1/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1986-87
      - Northwestern 1/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Penn State 1/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Lehigh 1/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Minnesota 2/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1987-88
      - Illinois 1/16/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Purdue 1/17/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Michigan State 1/19/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Indiana 2/14/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Ohio State 2/20/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Big Tens 3/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1988-89
      - Morgan State 1/13/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Northern Illinois 1/13/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Minnesota 2/03/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Northwestern 2/12/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Iowa State 3/05/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1989-90
      - Illinois 1/20/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Purdue 1/21/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Michigan State 1/23/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Wisconsin 2/25/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1990-91
      - Eastern Michigan 12/08/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Ferris State 12/08/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Lehigh 1/08/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Minnesota 2/10/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
    - 1991-92
      - Eastern Michigan & Morgan State 1/11/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Purdue, Illinois & Central Michigan 1/18/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Michigan State 1/21/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 39)
      - Cliff Keen Duels 2/8-9/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1992-93
      - Ferris State 1/09/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Lehigh 1/09/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Morgan State 1/09/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Penn State 1/16/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Minnesota 2/14/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1993-94
      - Ferris State, Morgan State & Eastern Michigan 1/08/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Michigan State 1/18/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Ohio State 2/04/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1994-95
      - Illinois 12/10/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Eastern Michigan, Morgan State & Lehigh 1/07/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Northwestern 1/28/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Minnesota 2/11/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1995-96
      - Central Michigan 1/19/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Ohio State 2/11/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Wisconsin 2/16/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Indiana 2/25/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1996-1997
      - Eastern Michigan 1/04/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Lehigh 1/05/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Penn State 1/12/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Michigan State 1/29/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Illinois 2/20/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1997-1998
      - Michigan State 2/04/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Purdue 2/07/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Indiana 2/20/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1998-1999
      - Michigan State 12/11/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Lehigh 1/17/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Illinois 1/31/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Michigan State 2/05/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Purdue 2/14/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Dale Bahr retirement 2/21/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Golf outing 3/02/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Big Tens 3/16-17/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1999-2000
      - Minnesota 2/11/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Indiana 2/12/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 40)
      - Michigan States 12/8/2000, digital files, 40 images, 2 original CompactFlash discs and copies on CD (Box 59)
    - 1997-1998
      (These negatives, acquired at a late date, may not have been taken by Bob Kalmbach)
      - Lehigh 1/5/1997, negatives (Box 40)
      - Penn St. 1/2/1997, negatives (Box 40)
      - Penn St. (?), negatives (Box 40)
      - Ohio State 2/2/1997, negatives
      - Catabrone at NCAA All-Star meet 2/3/1997, negatives (Box 40)
      - NCAA Championships 1997, negatives (Box 40)
      - NCAA Championships 1997, negatives (Box 40)
      - Purdue 2/7/1998, negatives (Box 40)
      - Indiana 2/20/1998, negatives (Box 40)
      - Big Ten Meet 1998, negatives (Box 40)
      - NCAA Championships 1998, negatives (Box 40)
  - U-M Women's Basketball photos
    - 1977-1978
      - Louisville 12/07/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Bowling Green 2/07/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Northwestern 2/25/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1978-1979
      - Detroit 12/02/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Western Michigan 12/13/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Adrian 12/18/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Northern Michigan 1/06/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Dayton 1/08/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Ohio State 1/15/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Notre Dame 1/20/1979, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
      - Michigan State 2/17/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 40)
    - 1979-1980
      - Grand Valley State 11/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Miami 12/01/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Detroit 12/13/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Illinois 12/15/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Bowling Green 12/22/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Wayne State 12/28/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - DePaul 1/05/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Louisville 1/28/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Northwestern 2/02/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Edinboro State 2/20/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 41)
    - 1980-1981
      - Windsor 12/02/1980, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Wisconsin 12/06/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Michigan State 1/06/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Kent State 1/14/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Oakland 1/20/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Indiana State 1/31/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Western Michigan 2/03/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 41)
      - Notre Dame 2/20/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Ohio State 2/24/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
    - 1981-1982
      - Jackson J.C. scrimmage 11/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Ferris State 12/01/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Cleveland State 12/08/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - DePaul 12/13/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Central Michigan 12/19/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Domino's Wolverine Classic 12/29-30/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Eastern Michigan 1/26/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Detroit 2/06/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Saginaw Valley State 2/18/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Illinois 2/27/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Northwestern 3/02/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
    - 1982-1983
      - Aus.? 11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Cleveland State 12/08/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Notre Dame 12/12/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Saginaw Valley State 12/18/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Domino's Wolverine Classic v. Toledo 12/29/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Northwestern 1/07/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Iowa 1/09/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Michigan State, 2/6 or 12/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Wisconsin 3/04/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
      - Minnesota 3/06/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 41)
    - 1983-1984
      - Western Michigan 12/03/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Central Michigan 12/06/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Detroit 12/17/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Domino's Wolverine Classic (Akron/Cincinnati) 12/29-30/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Wisconsin 1/15/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Purdue 1/27/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Northwestern 3/10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1984-1985
      - Northern Michigan 11/24/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Notre Dame 12/02/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Toledo 12/21/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Domino's Classic v. Nebraska 12/29/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Domino's Classic v. Eastern Michigan 12/30/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Illinois 1/11/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Northwestern 2/01/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Wisconsin 2/03/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Indiana 3/09/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1985-1986
      - Holy Cross 11/25/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Western Michigan 11/27/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Detroit 12/21/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Cleveland State 12/23/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1985-1986
      - Iowa State 12/28/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Indiana 1/03/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Ohio State 1/05/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Northwestern, Wisconsin 1/31-2/02 /1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Illinois 2/1986, contact sheet only (Box 42)
    - 1986-1987
      - Eastern Michigan 12/02/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Wayne State 12/11/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Purdue 1/02/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Indiana 2/06/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Ohio State 2/08/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Minnesota 3/01/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1987-1988
      - Oakland 12/01/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Ohio State 1/15/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Indiana 1/17/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Minnesota 2/05/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Iowa 2/07/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Illinois 3/10/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1988-1989
      - Toledo 12/01/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Western Michigan 12/06/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Auburn 12/13/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Ohio State 1/13/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Michigan State 2/24/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
      - Minnesota 3/11/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 42)
    - 1989-1990
      - Youngstown State 11/28/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Eastern Michigan 11/30/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Iowa 1/07/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Northwestern 1/19/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Ohio State 2/11/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1990-1991
      - Central Michigan 12/06/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Toledo 12/22/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - LaSalle 1/06/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Northwestern 1/11/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Ohio State 1/25/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Illinois 2/15/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Purdue 2/17/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Michigan State 3/07/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1991-1992
      - Cuba 11/14/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Notre Dame 12/13/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Pittsburgh 12/17/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Indiana State 12/21/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Purdue 1/10/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Iowa 1/26/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Indiana 2/28/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Ohio State 3/01/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1992-1993
      - Toledo 12/01/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Butler 12/21/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Detroit Mercy 1/04/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Indiana 1/08/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Minnesota 1/31/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Illinois 3/05/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1993-1994
      - Slovenia 11/23/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Marquette 12/18/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Illinois-Chicago 12/20/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Wisconsin 1/16/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Penn State 1/23/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Purdue 3/12/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1994-1995
      - Denmark 11/21/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Nebraska 12/08/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Kansas State 12/20/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Wisconsin 12/28/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Michigan State 1/06/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Northwestern 1/08/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Ohio State 1/22/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Penn State 2/10/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
      - Iowa 2/24/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 43)
    - 1995-1996
      - New Zealand 11/16/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - North Carolina 12/01/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/06/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Houston 12/15/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Canisius 12/21/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Iowa 12/29/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Penn State 1/14/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Minnesota 1/26/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Purdue 2/02/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Michigan State 2/18/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Wisconsin 2/25/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
    - 1996-1997
      - Rice 11/25/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Northwestern 1/03/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Illinois 1/12/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Indiana 1/17/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Wisconsin 1/24/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Purdue 2/09/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Penn State 2/14/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Minnesota 2/21/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Ohio State 2/23/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
    - 1997-1998
      - Illinois State 11/25/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Princeton 12/19/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Bowling Green 12/21/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Minnesota 12/30/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Penn State 1/04/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Minnesota 1/10/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Michigan State 1/18/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Iowa 1/25/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Indiana 2/01/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Northwestern 2/15/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
    - 1998-1999
      - Swiss 11/03/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Detroit 11/18/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Central Michigan 12/04/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Louisiana Tech 1/09/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Michigan State 1/20/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Illinois 2/12/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Indiana 2/21/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Michigan State 3/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Scrimmage,-11/23/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Holy Cross, 11./27/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Indiana 2/12/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Wisconsin 2/17/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Minnesota 1/30/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Northwester 2/27/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
      - Holy Cross 11/27/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 44)
    - 1999-2000
      - Hungary 11/12/1999, negatives (Box 44)
      - Indiana 2/13/2000, negatives (Box 44)
      - Wisconsin 2/13/2000, negatives (Box 44)
    - 2000-2001
      - Washington 11/19/2000, negatives (Box 44)
      - New Hampshire 12/01/2000, negatives (Box 44)
      - Syracuse.12/07/2000, negatives (Box 44)
      - Syracuse.12/07/2000, 69 digital image jpeg files, 2 original CompactFlash discs and copies on CD (Box 59)
  - U-M Volleyball photos
    - 1980
      - Indiana State 9/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1981